Mohamed Asmeer

I am a creative Web Developer. I have a strong passion for web development and hands-on experience with WordPress, including theme customization and plugin usage. With a solid foundation in HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript, I possess strong problem-solving skills, attention to detail, and the ability to work independently.

Work Experience

Junior Web Developer

Sri Lanka Railway Department (Jul 2024 - present)

- Developed a Seat Booking System using PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Designed a user-friendly interface and implemented responsive design.

Inventory System Administrator

Pioneer Hardware (Sep 2021 - Jan 2022)

- Managed and maintained the shop's inventory system to ensure accurate tracking of stock levels and product availability.
- Updated the system with new stock entries, product details, and supplier information, ensuring data integrity.

Educational Background

High National Diploma In IT

Sri Lanka Institute of Advanced Technological Education - Naiwala ATI 2021 - 2024

Diploma In Graphic Designing

Golden Collage Thihariya 2018 - 2019

Diploma In English

Thihariya International School 22021 - 2022

Projects

- Travel Agency Website Built Using WordPress Site Link - http://agency.wuaze.com/
- **E-Commerce site** Built Using WordPress Site link - http://asmeereshop.great-site.net/
- Train Block Seat Booking System Built Using PHP, CSS, MYSQL, JS Site Link - https://remis.railway.gov.lk/Seat Booking/index.php
- Hotel Management System Built Using C#, SQL
- Hotel Management Web Application Built Using HTML, CSS, JS, PHP (Laravel Framework), MYSQL

Contact

90/D Nasar mawatha, Udugoda, Ruggahawila. +94 723796453 mohamedasmeer325@gmail.com <u>Linkedin</u> || <u>GitHub</u>

Skills

Technical Skills

- · WordPress, HTML, CSS, JS
- PHP, JAVA, C#
- Photoshop, Illustrator
- MYSQL
- Laravel
- UI/UX Design

Soft Skills

- · Problem solving
- Time management
- Organizational skills
- · Creative thinking
- · Strong commitment

Tools/Sofware

- Office Software
- · Design Software
- Development Tools
- Digital Marketing Tools:

Certification/Short Courses

 University of Moratuwa Certified - Web Design, Frond End Web Development, Python For Beginner

Languages

- English
- Tamil
- Sinhala